360vouchercodes.co.uk 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy

## WHAT WE COLLECT

We may collect the following information: Email address other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.  
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.  
If you enter one of our competitions we will keep a copy of the data you submit to us.

## EMAILS

If you sign up for any of our newsletters or alerts, we will send you information about our voucher codes, deals, sales or other products and services we feel may interest you. Your e-mail address may also be used to send you information about our other websites that we feel are relevant to your registration on 360VoucherCodes.co.uk.   
You can sign up to our newsletter through submitting your email address at any of the sign up boxes featured throughout the website. By providing your email address you agree to receive regular newsletter emails from 360VoucherCodes.co.uk.   
You can unsubscribe from receiving our newsletter by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link featured within each of our newsletters.

 **Opt-out process**  
To unsubscribe from our newsletter please reply to one of our newsletters with 'UNSUBSCRIBE' in the subject line or click the "Unsubscribe" link featured at the bottom of the email.

## WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new deals, discounts, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.

## SECURITY

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## HOW WE USE COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@360vouchercodes.co.uk We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to . If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## DATA PROTECTION ACT 1998 (The "Act")

We make every effort to ensure that our practices, procedures and systems comply with the relevant data protection legislation and we are registered as a data controller for the purposes of the Act (Registration Number: ZA084017). We shall only use your personal data in accordance with the legal requirements, principles and best practice recommendations of the Act, which grants you various rights in respect of the processing of your personal data. For more details about your rights under the Act, the rules we have to adhere to in collecting and storing your information, and how you can check your data records, please visit <https://www.gov.uk/data-protection/the-data-protection-act>. You have a right to receive a copy of the information we hold about you by sending your request in writing, together with an administration fee of £10, to us at www.360vouchercodes.co.uk, Meade Ltd, Arena Business Centre, Nimrod Way, Wimborne, Dorset. BH21 7UH.

## CONTACING US

If you have any questions at all about this policy, or about how we use and process your personal information, please contact us at us by e-mail at info@360vouchercodes.co.uk or, alternatively, in writing to www.360vouchercodes.co.uk, Meade Ltd, Arena Business Centre, Nimrod Way, Wimborne, Dorset. BH21 7UH.
